

İbrahim Hulusi Oflaz

Software Developer

hulusioflaz200@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/ihoflaz

github.com/ihoflaz

+90 532 427 0449



İstanbul / Turkey



ihoflaz.com

Summary

I have been working in Software Development on various projects for about 3 years. Learning and utilizing innovative technologies always excite me. While progressing towards my goals, I value not only asking "How does it work?" but also asking "How can it work more efficiently?".

Projects

E-Commerce Infrastructure

I performed tests and installations for the E-Commerce Infrastructure project.

- Drupal Lando
- Nainx PHP
- Vagrant
- MySQL
- Docker

Advanced Order Management System

As a Fullstack developer, I developed an Advanced Order Management System with an Admin Dashboard that can automatically generate orders and manage orders and customers.

- ReactJS
- Prisma ORM Winston
- NextJS
- Material-UI ABAC IIS
- ExpressJS
 - Timestamped BullJS File Backup
- GoogleAPI

Visitor Tracking Form - CRM

I developed a module with CRM integration for the Cloud-Based ERP project.

- PostgreSQL Python •
- Docker MXX

ThinkTank

Our team of 5 people developed an opensource mobile application during an AppJam event, which can be used for educational purposes.

Flutter

- Dart
- Firebase

Commission Calc for E-Commerce

I developed a module by conducting | a competitor analysis for an E-Commerce Marketplace project.

- JavaScript Select2Menu
- **JQuery** Bootstrap5 Chart.JS

Experience

Frontend Developer -Hizmet Teknik Hırdavat | 06.2021 - 07.2022

During my role as a Frontend Developer in the E-Commerce Infrastructure project developed using Drupal, I had the opportunity to work with various technologies based on the company's needs.

- · HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- MySQL
- Docker
- **Bash Script**

Python Developer & System Admin -Hajans Yazılım ve Arge Teknolojileri | 07.2022 - 04.2023

I worked as both an ERP System Administrator and Python Developer in a cloud-based ERP project. In this role, I performed developments and installations based on the company's requirements and needs.

- Python
- Docker
- PostgreSQL
- XML

FullStack Developer -EtrSoft | 06.2023 - 10.2023

Developed an automated web application with an Admin Panel for managing esignature orders, facilitating dealer partnerships, and overseeing dealer-user relationships and transactions as a FullStack Developer.

ExpressJS

- ReactJS
- NodeJS

Education

08.2023 - Current Firat University

Software Engineering (Turkish)

08.2020 - Current **Anadolu University**

Web Design And Coding (Turkish)

Languages

- English (B1)
- · Turkish (Native)

Skills

Frontend Development

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootsprap
- ReactJS

Database

- MySQL
- PostgreSQL

Linux

- Bash Script
- System Admin

Backend Development

- Diango
- NodeJS

Software Development

- Python
- Flutter
- Dart
- Docker

Data Science With Python

- Numpy
- **Pandas**
- Matplotlib
- Scikit Learn